Register of the Friedrich A. von Hayek papers
Hoover Institution Archives
Friedrich A. von Hayek papers
1899-2005
86002
Hoover Institution Archives
146 manuscript boxes, 8 oversize boxes, 24 card file boxes, 5 envelopes, 16 videotape cassettes, 1395 digital files (.001 GB) (68.8 linear feet)
Diaries, correspondence, speeches and writings, notes, conference papers, conference programs, printed matter, sound recordings, photographs, and digital word processing files relating to laissez-faire economics and associated concepts of liberty, and especially to activities of the Mont Pèlerin Society. Also available on microfilm (139 reels). Sound use copies of sound recordings available.
Hayek, Friedrich A. von (Friedrich August), 1899-1992.
Access
Boxes 176-177 closed. Users must sign restriction agreement.
The remainder of the collection is open for research; materials must be requested at least two business days in advance of intended use.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Alternative Form Available
Also available on microfilm (139 reels).
Biographical Note
1899 May 8 Born, Vienna, Austria
1921 Dr. jur., Universität Wien, Vienna, Austria
1923 Dr. rer. pol., Universität Wien
1927-1931 Director, Österreichisches Institut für Konjunkturforschung (Austrian Institute for Economic Research)
1929 Author, Monetary Theory and the Trade Cycle Habilitation, Universität Wien
1929-1931 Lecturer in Economics, Universität Wien
1931 Author, Prices and Production
1931-1932 Guest Professor, University of London, England
1932-1950 Tooke Professor of Economic Science and Statistics, University of London, England
1935 Author, Collectivist Economic Planning
1937 Author, Monetary Nationalism and International Stability
1938 Naturalized British subject
1939 Author, Profits, Interest and Investment
1940 D. Sc. (Economics), University of London, England
1941 Author, The Pure Theory of Capital
1944 Author, The Road to Serfdom
1947-1962 President, Mont Pèlerin Society
1948 Author, Individualism and Economic Order
1950 Visiting Professor of Finance, University of Arkansas
1950-1962 Professor of Social and Moral Science, University of Chicago
1951 Author, John Stuart Mill and Harriet Taylor: Their Friendship and Subsequent Marriage
1952 Author, The Counter-Revolution of Science: Studies on the Abuse of Reason Author, The Sensory Order
1952-1953 Lecturer on Political Economy, Harvard University
1955 Author, The Political Ideal of the Rule of Law
1960 Author, The Constitution of Liberty
1962-1968 Professor of Economic Policy, Albert-Ludwigs-Universitat Freiburg i. Br., Germany
1967 Author, Studies in Philosophy, Politics and Economics
1968-1969 Visiting Flint Professor, University of California, Los Angeles
1969-1974 Guest Professor, Universität Salzburg, Austria
1973, 1976, 1979 Author, Law, Legislation and Liberty: A New Statement of the Liberal Principles of Justice and Political Economy (3 volumes)
1974 Joint Nobel Prize in Economics (with Gunnar Myrdal)
1977- Honorary Fellow, Hoover Institution on War, Revolution and Peace
1978 Author, New Studies in Philosophy, Politics, Economics and the History of Ideas
1984 Author, Money, Capital and Fluctuations
1988 Author, The Fatal Conceit
1992 Died
Scope and Content of Collection
The original accession of papers donated during the lifetime of Friedrich A. von Hayek, relates to laissez-faire economics and associated concepts of liberty, and especially to activities of the Mont Pèlerin Society as documented in diaries, correspondence, speeches and writings, notes, conference papers, conference programs, printed matter, sound recordings, and photographs. Materials of the same time periods may also be found in the Incremental Materials.
Scope and Content of Incremental Materials
The incremental materials of the Friedrich A. von Hayek papers constitute a significant part of the collection. The materials were received after Hayek's death from his family and his longtime secretary, Charlotte Cubitt. Consisting largely of correspondence, speeches and writings, notes, and digital word processing files, they document Hayek's career as an economist and his larger role as a public intellectual advocating free market principles and denouncing state intervention in matters of economic and social policy. The materials provide insight into the development of Hayek's thought as a leading figure of the Austrian School of Economics, and they also record the influence of his ideas on the political debates of his time, especially in the United States and Great Britain.
The Correspondence series in the incremental materials include exchanges of letters with fellow economists, publishers, and individuals active in the institutions with which Hayek was associated. Among the latter are colleagues and officials at the universities (London School of Economics, University of Chicago) where Hayek taught, as well as fellow members of the Mont Pèlerin Society, an organization founded by Hayek and in which he played a leading role for many years. The series contain Hayek's correspondence with economists associated with the Institute of Economic Affairs (Ralph Harris and Arthur Seldon, among others) and British politicians influenced by his ideas, including Margaret Thatcher. There is also extensive correspondence between Hayek and William W. Bartley, the editor of his final book, The Fatal Conceit. The incremental materials also include a separate correspondence series relating to Charlotte Cubitt, which dates from the last period of Hayek's life when he was in declining health.
The Speeches and Writings series in the incremental materials span nearly the whole of Hayek's prolific career as an author. They include early articles and book reviews, unpublished manuscripts on economics and psychology, and various prefaces and introductions prepared for foreign editions of his books. There are a number of speeches, as well as letters written to the editor of The Times of London. The series also contain drafts of such major works as The Road to Serfdom, the three volumes that comprise Law, Legislation and Liberty, and Hayek's final book, The Fatal Conceit. There are multiple versions of chapters of The Fatal Conceit, showing Hayek's corrections and revisions, and allowing for a comparison of Hayek's original conception of the work with its ultimate, published form, whose extensive editing has been the subject of some controversy. Additionally, the Reviews of Works By and About Hayek series in the second part of the incremental materials collects commentary on many of Hayek's published works. There is an abundance of reviews of The Road to Serfdom, most dating from the time of its original publication, but also some relating to subsequent editions, including translations. These articles show the success that the book achieved with the general public as well as demonstrating its impact on editorial and scholarly opinion at the time.
There is a significant amount of documentation on Hayek's personal and professional lives in the Biographical File series in the incremental materials. The second section contains many articles and clippings relating to Hayek, as well as some autobiographical writings, including a travel journal kept during a trip to France and Italy. In addition, there is a lengthy oral history consisting of extensive interviews with Hayek that were conducted by scholars under the auspices of the University of California at Los Angeles. There are also many clippings and other articles about Hayek in the Scrapbooks series of the second section of incremental materials.
The large Notes series in the second part of the incremental materials is comprised largely of notebooks, containing Hayek's notes on specific subjects, and a vast quantity of note cards, some of which relate to the writing of The Fatal Conceit. There are also many unsorted note cards pertaining largely to economics and philosophy, and whose diverse topics are indicative of the scope of Hayek's intellectual interests.
The Academic Career File series in the incremental materials contain lectures given by Hayek in his capacity as a professor of economics, including his earliest lectures in Great Britain. The Writings by Others series consist largely of articles, many of which touch on themes in Hayek's work. The second part of the incremental materials contains a Photographs series with numerous prints depicting Hayek, including ones relating to meetings of the Mont Pèlerin Society.
Mont Pèlerin Society.; Economic policy.; Economists.; Free enterprise.; Liberty.; Video tapes.
- Original Accession, 1906-1988
  Scope and Contents note
  The following materials comprise the original accession of papers donated during the lifetime of Friedrich A. von Hayek.
  - Biographical File I, 1961-1988
    Addresses, appraisals, articles, autograph requests, bibliographies, biographies, correspondence, itineraries, lists, memoranda, notes, schedules, clippings, and other printed matter, arranged alphabetically by physical form.
    - Addresses (Box-folder 1: 1)
    - Articles and clippings about or mentioning Hayek
      - undated (Box-folder 1: 2)
      - 1962 (Box-folder 1: 3)
      - 1974 (Box-folder 1: 4)
      - 1975 (Box-folder 1: 5)
      - 1976 (Box-folder 1: 6)
      - 1977
        - General (Box-folder 1: 7)
        - Argentina (Box-folder 1: 8)
        - Brazil (Box-folder 1: 9)
        - Chile (Box-folder 1: 10)
        - Portugal (Box-folder 1: 11)
      - 1979 (Box-folder 1: 12)
      - 1980 (Box-folder 1: 13)
      - 1981
        - Brazil (Box-folder 1: 14)
        - Chile (Box-folder 1: 15)
        - Venezuela (Box-folder 1: 16)
      - 1982 (Box-folder 1: 17)
      - 1983 (Box-folder 1: 18)
    - Autograph requests
      - 1964-1979 (Box-folder 1: 19)
      - 1980-1988 (Box-folder 2: 1)
    - Bibliographies (Box-folder 2: 2)
    - Biographies (Box-folder 2: 3)
    - Birthday cards and telegrams
      - 1964 (Box-folder 2: 4)
      - 1969 (Box-folder 2: 5)
      - 1974 (Box-folder 2: 6)
      - 1979 (Box-folder 2: 7)
      - 1984 (Box-folder 2: 8)
    - Honorary degrees - University of Dallas, Commencement program, 1975 (Box-folder 2: 9)
    - Honors
      - Österreichisches Ehrenzeichen für Wissenschaft und Kunst, Correspondence with Hertha Firnberg and Walter Brunner, 1974 (Box-folder 2: 10)
      - Verdienstmedaille des Landes Baden-Württemberg, correspondence with the Staatsministerium Baden-Württemberg, 1981 (Box-folder 2: 11)
      - Ehrenring der Stadt Wien, correspondence, including with Leopold Gratz and Dr. Sokolowski, 1983 (Box-folder 2: 12)
      - Member of the Order of the Companions of Honour, correspondence, including with Margaret Thatcher, Robert Fellows, Ralph Harris, John Raybould, and Great Britain. Embassy (Germany), 1984 (Box-folder 2: 13)
    - Itineraries (Box-folder 2: 14)
    - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 2: 15)
    - Notes (Box-folder 2: 16)
    - Prizes - Nobel, 1974
      - Letters of congratulation (Box-folder 3: 1-21)
      - Telegrams (Box-folder 3: 22)
    - Subject file
      - Guest professorship at the University of Salzburg, correspondence with Hertha Firnberg [See also Correspondence, Universität Salzburg], 1968-1974, 1977 (Box-folder 4: 1)
      - Negotiations regarding possible appointment to the University of Vienna. Correspondence with Heinrich Drimmel, Franz Hoyer, and Alexander Mahr, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 4: 2)
      - Personal library (eventually housed at the University of Salzburg)
        - Appraisal by Robert Rehberger, 1969 (Box-folder 4: 3)
          Includes correspondence.
        - Memoranda by Hayek, 1969-1983 (Box-folder 4: 4)
        - Correspondence
          - General, 1969 (Box-folder 4: 5)
          - Bosch, Bruno, 1969 (Box-folder 4: 6)
          - Coing, Helmut, 1983 (Box-folder 4: 7)
          - Evers, Dr., 1977 (Box-folder 4: 8)
          - Hahn, Carl H., 1983 (Box-folder 4: 9)
          - Hahnl, A., 1979 (Box-folder 4: 10)
          - Hegemann, Franz Josef (Stinnes Stiftung), 1983-1984 (Box-folder 4: 11)
          - Holbock, Carl, 1969 (Box-folder 4: 12)
          - Honsell, Heinrich, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 4: 13)
          - Koja, Friedrich, 1975 (Box-folder 4: 14)
          - Koppensteiner, Hans-Georg, 1977 (Box-folder 4: 15)
          - Kyrer, Alfred, 1980 (Box-folder 4: 16)
          - Mayer-Maly, Theo, 1968-1983 (Box-folder 4: 17)
          - Mock, Dr., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 4: 18)
          - Putz-Neuhauser, Gertrud, 1979 (Box-folder 4: 19)
          - Sompeck, Waltraud, 1979 (Box-folder 4: 20)
          - Toncic-Sorinj, Lujo, 1984 (Box-folder 4: 21)
          - Waldstein, Wolfgang, 1969 (Box-folder 4: 22)
          - Zipf, Heinz, 1983 (Box-folder 4: 23)
      - Trips
        - Japan, 1967-1981 (Box-folder 4: 24)
        - South Africa, with correspondence with the Free Market Foundation (Southern Africa), 1978 (Box-folder 4: 25)
        - South America
          - Undated schedule of program in Peru (Box-folder 4: 26)
          - Argentina, 1957 (Box-folder 4: 27)
          - 1961 (Box-folder 4: 28)
          - 1977 (Box-folder 4: 29)
            General note
            See also Oversize Material.
          - 1981
            - General (Box-folder 4: 30)
            - Argentina (Box-folder 4: 31)
            - Brazil (Box-folder 4: 32)
            - Chile (Box-folder 4: 33)
        - Taiwan, 1965-1975 (Box-folder 4: 34)
  - Correspondence I, 1923-1988
    Arranged alphabetically by name of correspondent. See also: Mont Pèlerin Society File, Correspondence.
    - General
      - Letters from readers or viewers regarding Hayek's appearances on television, articles, letters to the editor, speeches reviewed in the press, statements, etc.
        - undated (Box-folder 5: 1)
        - 1960s (Box-folder 5: 2)
        - 1974-1986 (Box-folder 5: 3-12)
      - Miscellaneous
        - A-C (Box-folder 5: 13-15)
        - D-H (Box-folder 6: 1-5)
        - I-Q (Box-folder 7: 1-9)
        - R-Z (Box-folder 8: 1-8)
    - Unidentified (Box-folder 8: 9)
      May include letters from Sir Ernest Barker, Alec L. Macfie, A. C. Pigou, and Dennis Robertson.
    - AB Timbro Publishing (John-Henri Holmberg, Peter Stein), 1983 (Box-folder 8: 10)
    - Abs, Hermann J., 1967-1969 (Box-folder 8: 11)
    - Academia de Ciencias Economicas (Ovidio Gimenez, Jose Heriberto Martinez, Guillermo Walter Klein, Julio H. G. Olivera, Jorge S. Oria, Alberto G. Servente), 1974-1982 (Box-folder 8: 12)
    - Academia Sinica (Shih-liang Chien), 1976-1982 (Box-folder 8: 13)
    - Accademia Nazionale dei Lincei (Enrico Cerulli, Giovanni Demaria, Giuseppe Roglia), 1971-1975 (Box-folder 8: 14)
    - Ackerman, P., 1963 (Box-folder 8: 15)
    - Acton, H. B., 1966 (Box-folder 8: 16)
    - Ad Hoc Sakharov Committee (Eugene P. Wigner and Sidney Ratner), 1985 (Box-folder 8: 17)
    - Adair, Douglass, 1962 (Box-folder 8: 18)
    - Adam Smith Bicentenary Committee (R. L. Briant), 1964, 1969 (Box-folder 9: 1)
      Includes correspondence with Thomas Wilson.
    - Adam Smith Conference (Thomas Wilson), 1965-1976 (Box-folder 9: 2)
    - Adam Smith Institute (Eamonn Butler, Barry Bracewell-Milnes), 1976-1984 (Box-folder 9: 3)
      Includes correspondence with G. V. Bayley, and the Adam Smith Club.
    - Adelstein, Richard Philip, 1985 (Box-folder 9: 4)
    - Adensamer, Norbert, 1984 (Box-folder 9: 5)
    - Adomeit, Klaus, 1969 (Box-folder 9: 6)
    - Advisory Council to the Unification Movement International [See International Conference on the Unity of the Sciences]
    - Africa Club, 1984 (Box-folder 9: 7)
    - Aims of Industry (Michael Ivens), 1983 (Box-folder 9: 8)
    - Ainsworth, Dennis William, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 9: 9)
    - Ajmone-Marsan, V., 1955 (Box-folder 9: 10)
    - Akiyama, Takao, 1979 (Box-folder 9: 11)
    - Aktion für Geistige und Psychische Freiheit (Ingo Heinemann), 1966 (Box-folder 9: 12)
    - Aktionsgemeinschaft Soziale Marktwirtschaft (Wolfgang Frickhoffer, Horst R. Gutermann), 1967-1983 (Box-folder 9: 13)
    - Albert, Hans, 1963-1982 (Box-folder 9: 14)
    - Albert Einstein Peace Prize Foundation (Bernard T. Feld, William M. Swartz), 1985 (Box-folder 9: 15)
    - Alchian, Armen A., 1979-1985 (Box-folder 9: 16)
    - Alessi, Louis de, 1979-1986 (Box-folder 9: 17)
    - Alexander von Humboldt-Stiftung (Wolfgang Holl), 1987 (Box-folder 9: 18)
    - Allais, Maurice, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 9: 19)
    - Alpine Forschungsstelle Obergurgl der Universität Innsbruck (Werner Heissel), 1968 (Box-folder 9: 20)
    - Alsogaray, Alvaro C., 1968 (Box-folder 9: 21)
    - Altenmuller, Eckeart, circa 1986 (Box-folder 9: 22)
    - Alternative Educational Foundation (R. Emmett Tyrrell, Jr.), 1983 (Box-folder 9: 23)
    - Alvarez, Louis W., 1984 (Box-folder 9: 24)
    - Amagin (Robert J. Chitester), 1983 (Box-folder 9: 25)
    - Amato, Luigi d', 1975 (Box-folder 9: 26)
    - American Academy in Rome (Laurance P. Roberts), 1954 (Box-folder 9: 27)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (Ralph W. Burhoe, J. L. Oncley, John R. Raper), 1961-1962 (Box-folder 9: 28)
    - American Council on Education (C. W. de Kiewiet), 1963 (Box-folder 9: 29)
    - American Economic Association (Franco Modigliani), 1974-1987 (Box-folder 10: 1)
    - American Economic Council (Kenneth J. Gerbino, Marsha Friedman), 1978-1982 (Box-folder 10: 2)
      Includes correspondence with the Austrian Economic Council Seminars.
    - American Economic Foundation (Fred G. Clark), 1962 (Box-folder 10: 3)
    - American Enterprise Institute (Gottfried Haberler), 1962-1988 (Box-folder 10: 4)
      Includes correspondence with Thomas F. Johnson.
    - American Geographical Society (Peter B. Corbin), 1975 (Box-folder 10: 5)
    - American Institute for Economic Research (E. C. Harwood), 1979-1982 (Box-folder 10: 6)
    - American Medical Association (C. Joseph Stetler, Leonard W. Martin, Louis S. Drake), 1962-1963 (Box-folder 10: 7)
    - American School of Classical Studies (John L. Caskey), 1955 (Box-folder 10: 8)
    - Americans for the National Voter Initiative Amendment (Chip Dent), 1978-1979 (Box-folder 10: 9)
    - Amerika-Haus Freiburg (Philip W. Carroll, George P. Clark, Horst Erich Richter), 1963-1966 (Box-folder 10: 10)
    - Amsel, H. G., 1963 (Box-folder 10: 11)
    - Anderson, Digby C., 1981 (Box-folder 10: 12)
    - Anderson, Robert B., 1983 (Box-folder 10: 13)
    - Anderson, Robert E., 1986 (Box-folder 10: 14)
    - Andre, J., 1976-1980 (Box-folder 10: 15)
    - Andreae, Clemens-August, 1964-1984 (Box-folder 10: 16)
    - Andrews, Gene, 1980 (Box-folder 10: 17)
    - Angelopoulos, Angelos, 1978 (Box-folder 10: 18)
    - Annan, Noel G., 1951-1952 (Box-folder 10: 19)
    - Antebi, Elizabeth, 1986 (Box-folder 10: 20)
    - Antoni, Carlo, undated (Box-folder 10: 21)
    - Aomi, Junichi, 1976-1986 (Box-folder 10: 22)
    - Araki, Milsuko, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 10: 23)
    - Arbeitsgemeinschaft Selbständiger Unternehmer (Herr Juchems, Dr. Mertens), 1967-1985 (Box-folder 10: 24)
    - Arbeitsgemeinschaft Sozialpädagogik und Gesellschaftsbildung (Hans-Friedrich Holters), 1976-1979 (Box-folder 10: 25)
    - Arbeitskreis Europaischer Studenten an der Hochschule St. Gallen (Dankwart von Schultzendorff, Michael Hoyer, Paschen von Flotow), 1980-1985 (Box-folder 10: 26)
    - Ardrey, Robert, 1966-1976 (Box-folder 10: 27)
    - Arndt, Helmut, 1979 (Box-folder 10: 28)
    - Aroma, Antonio d', 1975 (Box-folder 10: 29)
    - Aron, Raymond, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 10: 30)
    - Asahi Shimbun (Takashi Wada), 1985 (Box-folder 10: 31)
    - Asociacion Nacional de Fomento Economico (Guido Fernandez), 1965 (Box-folder 10: 32)
    - Association de la Libre Entreprise (G. J. Morisot), 1948-1954 (Box-folder 10: 33)
    - Association Internationale des Etudiants en Sciences Economiques et Sociales (Alfred Becker, Werner Pascha), 1980-1982 (Box-folder 10: 34)
    - Association Internationale pour l'Etude de l'Economie de l'Assurance (Orio Giarini), 1981-1984 (Box-folder 10: 35)
    - Associazione Bancaria Italiana (Gian Franco Calabresi), 1971-1977 (Box-folder 10: 36)
    - Atkinson, Rodney E. B., 1983 (Box-folder 10: 37)
    - Atlantic Economic Society (John M. Virgo), 1978-1979 (Box-folder 10: 38)
    - Atlas Economic Research Foundation [See Fisher, Antony G. A.]
    - August, Eugene R., 1974 (Box-folder 11: 1)
    - Auslands Österreicherwerk, 1980 (Box-folder 11: 2)
    - Austria. Botschaft (Germany), 1982-1984 (Box-folder 11: 3)
    - Austria. Botschaft (Japan), 1981 (Box-folder 11: 4)
    - Austria. Konsulat (Milan), 1984 (Box-folder 11: 5)
    - Austria Tabak (Paul Kruntorad), 1984 (Box-folder 11: 6)
    - Austrian Book Committee (S. Saxl, Georg Tugendhat, S. F. Winter), 1946-1948 (Box-folder 11: 7)
      Includes correspondence with Josef Stummvoll (Österreichische Nationalsbibliothek).
    - Austrian Economics Program at New York University Seminar [See Kirzner, Israel M.]
    - Austrian Economics Symposium, 1977 (Box-folder 11: 8)
    - Autrum, H., 1983 (Box-folder 11: 9)
    - Bachert, Gerd-Walter, 1976-1982 (Box-folder 11: 10)
    - Bachmann, Verena, re Vera C. Lutz, 1976 (Box-folder 11: 11)
    - Bachmeyer, A. C., 1950 (Box-folder 11: 12)
    - Badische Sparkasse- und Giroverband Mannheim (S. Kuhn), 1964 (Box-folder 11: 13)
    - Badrinath, Chaturvedi, 1985 (Box-folder 11: 14)
    - Bagiotti, Tullio, 1963-1978 (Box-folder 11: 15)
    - Bailey, Norman A., 1976 (Box-folder 11: 16)
    - Baillie-Grohman, H. T., 1961 (Box-folder 11: 17)
    - Ball-Wilson, Harry, 1981 (Box-folder 11: 18)
    - Ballou, F. William, 1979 (Box-folder 11: 19)
    - Ballve, Kate M. de, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 11: 20)
    - Banca dei Regolamenti Internazionali (Paolo Baffi) [See also Ente per gli Studi Monetari Bancari e Finanziari "Luigi Einaudi"], 1977 (Box-folder 11: 21)
    - Banca Nazionale del Lavoro (Luigi Ceriani), 1978-1980 (Box-folder 11: 22)
    - Bank Hofmann Zurich (G. Mahler, Markus R. Todtli), 1981-1983 (Box-folder 11: 23)
      Includes thank-you letters to the Bank Hofmann from people who received its reprint entitled "Friedrich A. von Hayek: Fünf Aufsätze."
    - Bank of Tokyo (Osamu Watanabe), 1981 (Box-folder 11: 24)
    - Banse, K., 1973 (Box-folder 11: 25)
    - Barger, Melvin D., 1977 (Box-folder 11: 26)
    - Bark, William C., 1980 (Box-folder 11: 27)
    - Barner, Martin, 1963 (Box-folder 11: 28)
    - Barth, Hans, 1962 (Box-folder 11: 29)
    - Bartlett, Frederic C., 1967 (Box-folder 11: 30)
    - Basile, Robert and Simonne, 1984 (Box-folder 11: 31)
    - Bassler, Herr, 1966 (Box-folder 11: 32)
    - Bauer, Peter T., 1962-1983 (Box-folder 11: 33)
    - Baum, Wilhelm, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 11: 34)
    - Baumann, Klaus, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 11: 35)
    - Baxter, Gordon, 1976 (Box-folder 11: 36)
    - Bayerischer Rundfunk (Otfrid Grabert, Isabel Muhlfenzl), 1978-1982 (Box-folder 11: 37)
    - Bayland Publishing (Peter C. Maffitt), re Ronald C. Nairn, 1980 (Box-folder 11: 38)
    - Beader, George, 1962 (Box-folder 11: 39)
    - Beaugrand, Philippe, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 11: 40)
    - Becker, Werner, 1982 (Box-folder 11: 41)
    - Beckmann, Walter, 1983 (Box-folder 11: 42)
    - Beddard, Robert, undated (Box-folder 11: 43)
    - Beg, A. S., 1966 (Box-folder 11: 44)
    - Begin, Menachem, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 11: 45)
    - Bellow, Saul, 1978 (Box-folder 11: 46)
    - Beltran-Florez, Lucas, 1970-1985 (Box-folder 11: 47)
    - Benedikter, Hans, 1962 (Box-folder 11: 48)
    - Benegas Lynch, Alberto, 1956-1985 (Box-folder 11: 49)
    - Benegas Lynch, Alberto, Jr., 1978-1987 (Box-folder 11: 50)
    - Benoist, Jean-Marie, 1986 (Box-folder 11: 51)